♪ [Music] ♪
Chet Rong here
with the Rong way to do Agile.
Today, requirements.
You should write specifications
for all development projects.
The more detail, the better.
Start with a marketing requirements document.
[folder slamming]
And a product requirements document.
Maybe throw in a design document, too.
[folder slamming]
Now, you are finally ready
to start writing your stories.
And remember, if your story
doesn't fit on a single card,
Then it is too short, so keep writing.
Don't be afraid to add
an amendment if needed.
And once everything is written down,
then there is no confusion.
- It says in 8.1.2.5.17 of the PRD
that it's supposed to have a hover state.
- How did I miss that?
- And most importantly, don't start coding
until everyone is signed off
on specifications.
- Ugh!
[crashing sound]
- That's the Rong way
to do requirements.
♪ [Music] ♪